[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS, INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
I…
kissed this man.
YEONG-DO
What's up?
Namgung!
Come to the karaoke.
Get over here right now!
-What are you doing? -Let go of me!
Punk!
-What the heck? -I'm so sorry.
I apologize.
I'm going crazy. I can't stop him now.
-Get here now! -Gosh.
Hang on. I'll be right there.
I don't know what you mean.
Were you dreaming or something?
You don't remember?
I tend to black out when I drink.
If I made a mistake, I apologize.
It didn't mean anything, so don't worry…
You really forgot?
I don't think so.
You look like you remember everything.
"I'll let you quit directing."
"I can do what your boyfriend
can never do for you."
Well?
Is it coming back to you?
I know you're confused.
I came here because I'm just as confused.
So I want to make a proposal.
Let's have some fun for a bit.
For you, a fling before marriage.
And for me, just enough entertainment
until I lose interest.
We'll keep it at that.
How about it?
What do you think?
-It wouldn't be too bad-- -You jerk!
Hey!
I regret what happened
so much that I could die.
So please,
stay out of my sight.
Please, please.
I'm begging you.
Please.
HONDURAS KARAOKE
The watch.
That damn watch he wears every single day.
All this fuss over that watch.
He's completely lost it.
He tore up the house, the salon, and now here.
Good thing Mom is on a trip.
Or she would've collapsed again.
You were wearing it until yesterday.
Yes, I was.
I don't know. It just disappeared.
It's not like Bo-ra bought it for you.
You got it when you joined the Gyenam City team.
Yeong-do.
How long are you going to live like this?
Do we have to keep walking on eggshells every time you flip out like this?
Bo-ra's ashes are in it.
Bo-ra's ashes
are inside the watch.
-Hey! -Huh?
No, wait…
-Follow me. -Wait.
-Wait a minute! -Come here.
Well…
There's this
challenge called "'99 Again"
that's trending.
So I borrowed Dad's suit,
but it felt incomplete.
Then I saw you sleeping,
and I saw the watch.
It looked so old and vintage,
so I just wanted to wear it for a bit and then put it back.
So where is it? Where's the watch now?
Hey, yelling at him won't solve anything.
Lee Sang-su, answer me straight.
You lost the watch, didn't you?
No, I mean…
I had it on when I was filming,
but then it suddenly disappeared. I was scared--
Hey!
Why are you yelling at me?
Why are you crying? Stop crying!
You, too. Calm down.
He can't speak if you yell at him.
Yeong-do, if I don't find that watch,
I won't let this go.
I'm done with you two.
Hey.
You're saying that to your brother over some watch?
"Some watch"?
Both of you, stop.
Fighting like this won't solve anything.
Sang-su, stop crying.
It's getting late.
Let's check the stream first thing tomorrow.
Sang-su, send me all the footage.
We need the exact spot to narrow the search.
Stop crying. What are you even crying for?
What if Aunt Bo-ra comes for me?
I'm scared.
That won't happen.
He said Aunt Bo-ra's ashes were in the watch.
I had no idea.
I wore it and danced to "Boom Boom Boom."
I even did Bollywood dances.
That Bo-ra…
She never visited Wan-do in four years.
Don't worry.
But since I lost the watch,
she might come to punish me.
Then tell her to go see your uncle.
Actually, no.
Sang-su.
If Aunt Bo-ra pays you a visit,
you have to beg her
not to go see your uncle.
What?
No way.
Why would you say that?
I'm scared!
Stop crying and tell her exactly this.
Tell her to stay away from Wan-do.
To please let him live in peace.
To please just leave him alone.
Why are you doing this? It's scary.
Your mom's side is Catholic.
We have six priests in the family.
You'll be fine, Gabriel.
Look, I'm sorry!
Stop it!
Come on, let's go.
Gabriel…
Mi-do, you asleep?
You never go to sleep before 2 a.m.
I'm completely done with that woman.
I'll never see her again.
Hey, are you crying?
Why are you crying? You're making me sad.
Namgung, what happened to your face?
Did she do that?
It's all over now.
You won't have to worry about this ever again.
So please stop crying.
Don't cry.
6. WHO IS OUR BEST HERO?
Take a look at this.
I trusted her to close up,
but she was secretly taking customers late at night.
Unbelievable.
What are you doing?
I was going to call the cops,
but I called the family contact on your resume first.
So ungrateful.
What will you do?
Are you going to pay
3.2 million won?
She's not family.
She's a friend.
Talk to me.
Call the cops.
That'll teach her a lesson.
ATM
Please take your card. Cash will be dispensed.
Please take your cash.
CASH DISPENSER
Thank you for your transaction. Have a nice day.
Su-a.
The salon owner does this a lot.
We fought over my days off.
She promised to help with my training,
then she treated me like a thief.
You…
don't believe me, do you?
Then earn my trust.
With the CCTV footage,
your online post, the contract,
and how you ignored the owner's calls,
how can I trust you?
HYDROCOLLOID BANDAGE
Don't use the bandage on your face.
It'll scar your pretty face.
I'll get my things tomorrow when you go to work.
I'll pay you back soon, too.
Sorry for bothering you.
I won't ever…
contact you again.
Make sure you eat. Eat everything even if you're not hungry.
And take your red ginseng.
Mi-do has been acting weird.
Why?
Because you met your mom?
Still? That was days ago.
Yes, but…
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Looks good.
What's wrong, Mi-do?
Why do you keep crying?
Mi-do cries whenever she sees me these days.
She just
keeps crying.
Is she going through menopause?
Lots of women get it in their thirties.
Come on.
Don't be ridiculous.
How else can you explain it?
Why would a tough girl like her cry every day?
You were crying every day too after the divorce. Remember?
Why would you bring that up now?
What about you?
Sulking because of your nephew.
I heard you ignored Sang-su's text last night.
That kid…
Tell him to stay away.
Hey, man, he's 14 years old.
Aren't embarrassed to be fighting with a kid?
What about you?
You fight with that kid. Aren't you embarrassed?
Oh, you little punk.
Keep going.
Why don't you keep going?
Why don't you do it right?
Don't half-ass it.
Should I call Ms. Ma, Mi-do, and Sang-su, all of them?
Jeez, seriously.
You guys fight every day.
-Where is it? -Namgung.
Are you…
okay?
What? I can't hear you.
I mean…
you met with your mom.
Right. Ho.
Are you okay?
I heard she caused trouble again.
Nothing serious, right?
Of course it's serious.
A warrant was issued, and she's in a detention center.
Hey!
-You scared me. -If that happened,
you should've told us right away.
You just said you saw her,
so I thought it was just about money again.
Why are you always like this?
Does Mi-do know?
She's been acting weird because of you.
Why are you like this?
Always telling us when it's over.
Didn't I tell you never to do that again?
Stop doing that.
We're friends. It really hurts.
I'd feel so pathetic telling you.
The fact that a woman like her is my mom
is just so pathetic and embarrassing.
I feel so pathetic and embarrassed
in front of you and Wan-do,
and especially in front of Mi-do.
So I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, jeez.
Goodness.
Say that one more time.
I'll seriously get mad.
Yes, I'll get mad, too!
I was too embarrassed to tell you this,
but in the last civil service exam I failed,
my average wasn't 55. It was 37.
Yes, and I was too embarrassed to say this too,
but my driving test…
I didn't fail four times. I failed seven times.
You took the civil service exam for three straight years and got a 37?
Are you even an athlete?
How do you fail a driving test seven times?
That's hilarious, man.
Hey, get that punk.
-Hey! -Get him!
No!
-Get him! -Wait!
Time out!
Ouch!
Hey, the watch!
I won't fall for that twice, punk!
No, I'm serious! Look!
How many meters today?
210 meters.
Still so deep.
When we scattered Bo-ra into the sea…
something got caught in my hand.
THE LATE BAEK BO-RA
Bo-ra…
No, Bo-ra!
I'm really pathetic, aren't I?
I regret what happened
so much that I could die.
Stay out of my sight.
Damn it.
Let's discuss the case about the researcher in person.
Not over the phone.
The researcher isn't the issue.
Didn't you hear about Jisang?
Things are looking bad at Jisang.
I think something went wrong.
Last night, the cops and the Financial Supervisory Service
raided Line's accounting HQ and seized all their servers.
Didn't Mr. Seo tell you anything?
Hello?
Are you listening?
Gosh, is he listening or not?
Mr. Han, why don't you take a vacation?
You know…
you haven't had a break since the Cheonsong Electronics case.
Let Attorney Lee finish up Jisang's case.
Get some fresh air for two weeks.
We still have the appeal.
I have to settle this.
Jisang's cash flow
will be cut off once the damages claim is enforced.
Mediation is the only option.
Chairman Ko will accept it soon.
I didn't expect to be sent off empty-handed like this.
What was that?
You have no conscience.
You worked me to the bone.
You should at least get me a business-class ticket.
I'll get you first class.
Just say the word. Where to?
I don't want anywhere too hot.
Or too humid.
So I'm a dog?
A lapdog, to be exact.
A lapdog who could get dumped by his master any second.
Hi.
This is a piece called a knight in a game called chess.
It's the most unpredictable piece in chess.
The knight.
A rook can only move in straight lines,
but not this one.
Even when it seems completely blocked,
it moves in an L-shape
to create a chance.
It may look like a dead end, but it's not over.
Even if it doesn't go straight,
it can freely change the game as it moves on the board.
I'm here…
to give you
that chance right now.
Whether you tell me the truth or not,
I plan to make it happen.
So trust me now,
and tell me what happened to you that night.
Will you?
Mi-do, are you up?
Still not feeling well?
MIDORI
Want to get chicken feet from Bongcheon later?
46TH COHORT LEE MIN-GI: DID YOU SEE THE JOB POST FOR THE POSITION IN FRANCE?
Did you see the job post for the position in France?
What are you looking at so intently, Mr. Namgung?
EXPAT POSITION IN PARIS CONFECTIONERY MARKETING & SALES
Are you applying for it?
I'm thinking about it. The perks are pretty good.
Wow, you traitor.
What about our Spicy SweeTato Chips?
I was going to bail if it didn't launch by Q3 next year anyway.
You're so bold when the boss is away.
I'm telling on you.
You probably wouldn't get it anyway.
I heard about this from a friend in HR.
They need a French speaker.
I double-majored in French.
What?
My GPA was 4.3.
I wiped the floor with the French majors.
What?
Why are you so fluent? Why is your accent so good?
-Are you-- -Are you really going?
Why?
Launching isn't the end.
What about marketing? Pop-ups?
Wow, were you always this irresponsible?
Or is it because of ambition?
Because expats are first in line for promotions?
Or is it the salary?
If not that, is it the MBA tuition support?
Is it because of that?
It's on my girlfriend's bucket list.
My girlfriend has always wanted to live in Paris.
She's been down lately.
Two years there would be a nice change of pace.
Will the competition be tough?
Mr. Namgung.
Are you getting married?
You are, right?
Wow, congratulations!
Pretend you don't know.
If the boss knows I didn't tell him, he'll pout for a week.
You're finally off the market.
Seriously, congratulations.
Isn't your girlfriend your first love?
You don't have an appointment.
I'm asking because he won't answer!
Assistant Manager Namgung Ho with TF Snack Team 3!
If you keep making a scene, we'll have to call the police.
Want to see a real scene?
Just make one phone call!
-You need to leave. -What?
-I warned you. -Leave?
-Leave where? -Why?
-Call the cops! -Okay.
-Get out. -You want to do this?
-Hit me. -You punk!
Well, look who it is.
Our precious debtor.
You're much more handsome in person.
Nice to meet you.
Let's take this outside.
Namgung, I'm at a cafe near your office.
I'll write here until you're off work.
Let's get dinner.
Did Mr. Namgung take out a private loan?
No way.
I worked with him at the pop-up. He's definitely not like that.
Then why would a loan shark come here?
We all saw it.
He must have his reasons.
Come to think of it, when Assistant Manager Gung was new,
I heard something similar happened.
What?
He was the first rookie to get his paycheck garnished.
There was a lot of talk in the finance team.
I think I heard about that too.
Was he gambling?
Like sports betting or something?
You know, those clean-cut guys usually have dirty secrets.
Knock it off.
Don't gossip when you don't know anything.
I'm embarrassed to be your coworker.
Focus on your own work instead of gossiping.
-That scared me. -Seriously.
Excuse me.
The person you are calling is unavailable. Please leave a message…
At what time did he leave with those guys?
Less than 20 minutes ago. I'm sure he's fine.
If it was serious, we'd have called 911.
He said not to worry.
You still should've called 911.
Anything could happen.
You're worrying too much.
In broad daylight in Seoul? What could…
But what if something does happen?
What if something happens to Namgung?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't take it out on you. I'm just so worried.
I'm sorry. I really am.
PROMISSORY NOTE STANDARD LOAN AGREEMENT
Your mother,
Choi Hwa-young, borrowed 300 million won.
You know she's in custody, right?
She'll be short on the interest payment starting this month,
so we came a bit early.
If you lent money to a con artist without collateral,
wasn't that a risk you were willing to take?
Who knew she'd blow it before she even started?
I hear you're the one who messed it up.
Then you should take the fall.
By the way, you know renouncing your inheritance won't work, right?
We don't care about the law--
Seeing a guy like you reminds me of someone.
This is the tibialis posterior.
-What? -My biological father
was supposedly great at cutting it.
Guess he was a famous knifeman in your line of work.
He crippled a ton of people.
Choi Hwa-young said
it was creepy how he'd giggle while he worked.
Are you threatening me?
It's not a threat.
I'm just saying my blood is trash.
Look, you think words like that would make us flinch?
-We've seen tons of guys-- -I'm sure you have.
But I'm different.
I'm very different.
You probably know,
but I only have one kidney.
I'm not giving up my liver or eyes.
And you'd better not mess with the people around me.
Who do you think you are?
Why so confident?
You have no idea what we can do.
Sorry, but…
I already died when I was seven,
so I'm living on borrowed time.
That's why…
I'm not afraid of dying.
Mess with me and see.
I'll show you how crazy I can get.
Excuse me!
Seriously, congratulations.
Isn't your girlfriend your first love?
"First love…"
is a bit too cheesy.
If I had to describe her,
maybe a hero?
My girlfriend is really awesome.
It's impossible
for you not to…
fall so hard for her.
Lee Mi-do was the greatest hero in my life.
After I died at seven, she revived me and then kept on saving me over and over.
She's truly the greatest hero in my life.
Die, you little shit!
Damn you! My gosh.
You little piece of shit.
Namgung, are you okay?
Namgung. Oh no.
Are you all right?
Mi-do.
But since he's a minor, he'll be released soon, right?
Everything he said is a lie.
Namgung Ho was taking his midterms
during the time the victim was texting them.
The account is in Namgung Ho's name, but Aunt Hwa-young used it.
The evidence is all here. Please check it.
Damn it.
What are you smiling at?
You almost went to juvie.
Ho!
If you don't pay interest this month,
you'll never see your son again.
Then lend me another million won.
What?
You're taking my son as collateral anyway.
Lend me one million… No, two million.
Ho, Mom will come get you, okay?
Lend it to me.
I feel bad for you.
For having a mom like that.
A kid jumped out.
-Are you okay? -What the…
This is so freaking annoying.
Hey!
You know Granny Yong-seon from Busan, right?
How do you know Ms. Yong-seon…
MS. YONG-SEON FROM BUSAN
Yes, ma'am.
Yes.
Sorry?
Understood.
I'll call you back.
We'll pay off the debt.
We'll pay monthly interest, too.
But…
we'll only pay the legal interest rate along with the principal.
Mi-do, get up.
Stay out of this. Get up.
So don't ever show up at his work like this again.
If… you come here and lay a finger on him,
you're dead.
I'll really kill you.
Mi-do.
I guess I anticipated this
when I wrote a script involving loan sharks.
Wow, I had such great foresight.
Even though the movie fell through,
sending Granny Yong-seon red ginseng every holiday paid off.
Namgung.
I'll work hard on my writing.
I'll swallow my pride and debut.
We can pay it off together, okay?
Don't you dare get any crazy ideas.
Don't even think about selling your liver or something.
I know why you delayed our marriage.
You said we'd wait until I debuted.
That was just an excuse.
It was because of your mom.
You thought you'd burden me.
I actually knew everything. I just pretended not to.
Honestly,
I was a little scared.
But not anymore.
I'm really not scared anymore.
Don't say you're sorry.
Don't say thank you, either.
Just…
don't say anything.
Don't say anything.
Let's go on a trip.
A trip?
Yes.
Let's go to Taipei.
It was great three years ago.
Let's do all the sightseeing we missed last time.
Like…
the Shilin Night Market.
And the place from Spirited Away. What was it called?
-Jiufen? -Yes, let's go there, too.
Can you get time off?
You're busy at work.
I'll make it happen.
Let's go.
Really.
Hello?
What? She answers this number?
Wow, that hurts my pride.
This is so annoying.
Gosh…
Come on, give it to me.
Hello?
Do you live at Hines Officetel?
I think you need to come outside.
Excuse me?
I'm in front of Hines Officetel,
and my passenger is drunk.
Hello, I--
-Are you the one who answered the call? -I am.
Why did it take you so long? I called so many times.
He must've lost his wallet. He hasn't paid me yet.
I'm sorry, but could you take him back to where he was?
I'll pay for a round trip.
That's a problem.
I accepted a call when we spoke.
If I cancel it now, I'll get a penalty.
You can wire it to my account. It's 35,000 won.
Oh, okay. Just a second.
I sent it.
Lee Mi-do, right?
-Yes. -It went through.
-Take care. -You too.
Just so you don't get the wrong idea,
I'm only doing this because I hate you being in my space.
What the hell am I doing at this hour?
Jeez.
What?
It really is Lee Mi-do.
Mr. Han, you're very drunk. We can talk later.
Later when?
You blocked my number.
I have a lot of pride, you know?
I'd never call you
using someone else's phone.
That's the best thing I've heard from you.
Make sure you keep that promise.
This is annoying.
You're not my type.
I don't even like older women.
What?
I'm telling you,
you're not my type.
Okay.
I admit you're cute.
No, no.
I admit you're really cute.
No.
You're not cute at all.
This is so annoying.
Don't laugh at me.
No, do it again.
Mr. Han.
It's just that
you've never met a crazy bitch like me,
so you're just confused.
In a few days,
you'll just think, "Oh, there was that crazy bitch,"
and you'll forget my face.
So,
just pretend you had cheap booze
and got a bad stomachache,
and forget about it.
Want me to tell you a secret?
I'm getting dumped soon.
Go ahead and laugh.
It's pretty funny.
I missed you.
You just kept…
driving me crazy.
I kept…
and kept…
Just kept…
Kept…
I missed you.
You just kept…
Good morning!
Morning.
MANAGER EOM HO-SIK
-Good morning. -Hey.
All right…
Can we talk?
About the incident in the lobby yesterday,
I took care of it myself.
If HR Manager Jeong glares at you,
just ignore him and move on.
Wait, what?
Did you plead with him for me?
And about those posts on the company intranet,
they agreed to delete them right away.
Best not to look. Stay off it for now.
Don't tell me you talked to Manager Shin from DX.
Plus, under current company rules,
they can't garnish your wages.
So don't worry too much about that.
Wow, even Finance Manager Yeom?
Are you okay?
Need anything else?
I want the Paris posting.
I know my chances are ruined because of this incident.
But if you beg General Manager Kang, who knows?
Since you're already begging,
push a little harder for me.
Tell them I really want to go.
I'll swat you all the way to Paris!
I'm just joking.
Hey, do you know
what I went through because of you yesterday?
I love you. Thank you.
Without you, I'd be dragged to HR
and sent to the Cheonan factory.
I'm nothing without my suit. That was close.
What do you mean, "That was close"?
Hey, just get lost, will you?
Why do I even bother talking to you?
Gosh.
Speaking of which,
you're approving my six-day leave starting tomorrow, right?
I asked days ago. Why no approval yet?
I already bought my plane tickets. Come on, please hurry.
Hey!
Are you some travel vlogger?
What kind of bullshit are you spouting?
That guy…
LOVE EAT
Where did Pudgy go?
Did she get taken?
Bambi was hospitalized.
She has the herpes virus.
It's common for cats.
Anyway, she's at the vet.
Is it bad?
It was at first.
But she's fine now. She's eating well.
Get her spayed while she's there.
Is that really all you have to say to me?
I'll be off for six days.
Don't be late on the seasoning mix report.
I'll check with Sang-hun.
I'll help you get that Paris posting.
What?
I looked into who's testing the waters for the expat position.
Your experience and qualifications are far superior.
So?
I'll make sure you're fully prepared for the interview.
The person who went to Germany was my mentor…
Why not?
You wanted to go to Paris.
Ms. Ko got in by acing her interview.
Ko Yun-jae?
Her husband is Director Im's wife's nephew.
Sorry?
Just figuring that out, my naive little junior?
Jeez.
I never even dreamed of getting the Paris position anyway.
I just want
the launch next year to be successful
so I get a bonus… Hey, why the tears?
I really wanted you to go.
Why are you--
I really…
I really wanted to help you go.
Hey, don't cry…
Come on.
Everyone's staring.
Let's go over there.
Are you looking for something?
I need a gift for my boyfriend.
Something long-lasting that won't wilt.
Long-lasting? A dwarf umbrella tree.
It symbolizes luck and prosperity, so it makes a great gift.
DWARF UMBRELLA TREE
And the green color is calming, so it's good for stress, too.
It's nice and shiny, right?
Will it last forever?
Of course. It grows well in the shade, too.
With good care, it'll last a long time.
I'll take it.
Wow, that was fast.
To celebrate our opening, customers who spend over 80,000 won
get a free gift.
Thank you.
Depending on the ball's color,
you win a chrysanthemum, plant food, or a saucer.
Do I just press this button?
Yes, just press the button.
Damn it.
Are you crazy?
What's this?
A voice recorder.
I'll give you some plant food.
Ma'am!
I just spoke with the detective in charge of Ms. Choi.
Ms. Choi stated that Ms. Lee helped fund the fraud for two years.
You said you recorded your last meeting with Ms. Choi.
Can you send me that file?
Yes, I'll send it now.
Oh, right.
The laptop's broken.
Damn it…
MIDORI
Do you know what you just did?
Oh, come on.
You don't want to direct, do you?
You're scared, aren't you?
I WAS SO IMPRESSED
INDIE FILM'S NEW HOPE A FAN AS OF TODAY
LEE MI-DO IS THE BEST
I knew it. You're scared.
No, I'm not.
THE LINES DELIVER THE STORY
That's not it.
Yes, you are.
You want to run away.
WHAT IS A MOVIE?
You're scared and terrified.
I LIKED THE ENDING WHEN THEY PART I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR NEXT PROJECT
But you feel bad for your boyfriend,
so you're too ashamed to do it.
Am I wrong?
You're wrong.
Want me to help you escape?
You were desperate enough to go beg Song Hae-na,
but I got in the way and ruined it.
You can say you had the talent but just got unlucky.
You got tangled up with some crazy guy,
and got completely screwed over.
Burying a rookie director before they even start
is incredibly easy for me.
Why would you go that far for me?
What do you want from me?
One thing is for sure.
It's not because of the settlement.
DWARF UMBRELLA TREE
You said nothing happened.
That I had nothing to worry about.
I'll just disappear from your life.
I said I'll get out of your life!
What is your problem?
I'm terrible, aren't I?
You must be disappointed.
Ms. Lee and I aren't like that.
Not buying it?
I know everything I say will be an excuse.
Just how miserable do you want to make me?
Mi-do.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
Subtitle Translation by Cayle Kim